The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Master !
I was hurt by someone !
Master, please avenge me !
Tell me what happened.
That prince's lackey escaped.
I was investigating, so I chased him.
I didn't think he would have strong backup.
He asked a mortal for help
and he injured me.
Master,
if Fu'er hadn't escaped in time,
I'm afraid Master wouldn't have ever seen me again.
Are you sure
that when you saw this cultivator,
he had no spiritual energy
as if he were a mortal ?
I'm not mistaken !
Otherwise, why would I think he's a mortal ?
Lead the way.
No need to fly,
we will walk.
We haven't walked together in a long time.
See you, Master.
Master favors Junior Brother too much.
Since he was a child,
when he got in trouble,
Master would help him immediately.
Over the years, he never refused him anything.
With Master's wisdom,
how could he not understand what Junior Brother was doing ?
There must be something wrong.
I wonder which sect the person who provoked Junior Brother belongs to.
I guess he must be at Core Formation
since he was able to beat Junior Brother.
With Master's standing in the Four Sect Alliance,
not to mention a Core Formation cultivator,
even a Nascent Soul cultivator
won't stand a chance.
You dared to provoke me.
I will make you pay for it with your life !
Candy animals !
Look, it's the candy maker.
How much for a candy ?
One copper coin is enough.
Fu'er was born the year of the monkey,
of course I had to choose this one.
Do you like it ?
When I first met you,
you were fighting with a bunch of kids over candies.
Maybe you have already forgotten...
How could I forget ?
Fu'er lived a hard life.
If it weren't for Master,
I'm afraid I'd be dead by now.
Let's go.
Take me to that person.
Tell me.
What happened ?
It's because of the Rain Cauldron.
The Rain Cauldron ?
The Crown Prince obtained a precious artifact
named the Rain Cauldron.
The law in the Four Sect Alliance
is to gift the Prince any Immortal artifact you find.
The Crown Prince was betrayed in a moment of carelessness.
He had hidden the Rain Cauldron
but it was discovered by Zhou Wutai of the White Cloud Sect.
He ordered to kill the Crown Prince to bury the evidence.
The Crown Prince offered to give him the Rain Cauldron
but he couldn't escape death.
The cultivators who supported us before
left us one by one.
I had no other choice
but to come and ask for help from Mister Wang.
I saved your life
to repay for your 16 years of commitment.
You can leave now.
Thank you for your kindness !
I will remember it forever.
Come back in.
We have guests.
Master,
it's him !
He's the one who hurt me !
Fellow cultivator,
how about we have a drink ?
Sounds good ?
Good wine !
Since you like it,
I'll gift you the rest of that jug.
Fellow cultivator's cultivation level is much higher than mine.
I admire you for living like a mortal to turn into a mortal.
Fellow cultivator is turning into a mortal
by using the teacher-disciple emotion to understand the heavens.
Your result is the same as mine,
you don't have to admire me.
It seems I was not wrong.
When I heard my disciple,
I guessed there was someone in the same realm as me
that is trying to reach Soul Formation.
Why don't you and I have a competition ?
Let's see who will reach the mythical Soul Formation realm first.
Interested ?
If I feel a sense of competition in my heart,
I'm afraid I will never reach Soul Formation in my life.
Fellow cultivator,
your words are
very vicious.
I didn't expect to meet
a cultivator of your caliber here.
I am Zhou Wutai.
I wonder what fellow cultivator's name is.
Wang Lin.
Fellow cultivator Wang.
Within a hundred years,
you will definitely reach Soul Formation !
I will congratulate you early today.
Another vicious word attack.
If these words plant a seed in my heart,
it will be a curse for a hundred years.
As the years pass and I fail to reach Soul Formation,
I will slowly lose my chance to breakthrough
if I don't have a sudden enlightenment.
Fellow cultivator Zhou is speaking prematurely,
From my point of view,
whether fellow cultivator Zhou can reach Soul Formation
is uncertain.
But your disciple
will definitely die
within a hundred years.
Mister Wang has a sharp tongue.
But if he makes Zhou Wutai angry...
what will happen ?
He saw through my relation with Fu'er,
that I'm acting as his teacher and father.
This person is understanding the heavens
through the teacher-disciple releationship
to form his domain.
He raised him with his love,
his kindness to give him favor,
his heart to love him.
But he is plagued with sorrow.
Because everything he has done,
is for the sake of
his teacher-disciple realationship.
But the day he will finally form his domain,
when he will be about to reach Soul Formation
will be the day he has to kill his disciple himself.
By killing the disciple he placed all his heart in,
the sorrow will fill his whole being
while he takes that last step and reaches Soul Formation.
This person's domain
appears emotionate
but is ruthless.
Yet amidst that ruthlessness,
is the emotion of true love.
By bringing the hundred year limit,
he exposed my true ruthless nature
and the sadness I will feel in the future.
At the same time,
he left a mark in Fu'er's heart.
He saw through me
but I didn't get a single clue about his domain.
He's clever...
Very clever.
Tell your king
to send the Rain Cauldron to my temple in 3 days.
And I
won't pursue this matter.
Master !
But your disciple
will definitely die
within a hundred years.
Fu'er,
don't think about it too much.
Why didn't you eat the candy ?
Master gifted it to me
so I plan to keep it forever.
This person shall be my lifelong rival.
I knew that Mister Wang was an expert !
The White Cloud Sect cultivators
didn't dare to help us anymore
and the Crown Prince was killed.
But with a few words,
he made this cultivator comply.
The Desperate Emotions Domain...
The Comfort Domain...
The Passing of Time Domain...
What will
my domain be ?
5 years later
Shopkeeper Wang.
Mother.
Widow Ceng Si,
greets Brother Wang.
Condolences.
Brother,
excuse him.
The kid doesn't understand.
Brother,
if you don't mind,
come over for a meal.
Uncle Wang...
You're not a cultivator
so you have to enter the reincarnation cycle.
This flower will help your soul in the Reincarnation River
to find a good family.
Grandpa ?
What is this place ?
I cannot believe someone on this waste of a planet
can comprehend such a profound Dao.
The All-Seer\NTian Yunzi
But with your mere Nascent Soul cultivation,
it's best not to be too greedy.
This kind of heavenly Dao
it will take you millions of years to find its source.
But your body will already have rotted away.
Have you thought of that ?
I am the All-Seer.
Since we met, let's make a deal.
If you can get off this waste of a planet
then come find me on planet Tian Yun to become my honorary disciple
and follow me for 100 years.
Go back.
If it weren't for the All-Seer pushing me back,
I would have lost myself
to search for the source of the Dao of the reincarnation cycle.
I did it !
Wang Lin's avatar\NPeak Late stage Nascent Soul
After thinking so much, I understand.
The passing of time
is just an imitation of the reincarnation cycle
but it's not like a real reincarnation.
I still need to pursue my own domain.
Soul Formation...
I, Wang Lin,
will definitely reach it.
The days of the mortal world always go by quickly.
To improve his blacksmith business
Da Niu annexed 3 other shops nearby.
He is thriving.
Da Niu also violated his family's rule
by passing on his skills to other people, and have them work for him.
Dad,
I don't want to be a blacksmith.
I want to learn wood carving !
You cannot even hold a forge hammer properly,
yet you want to do fine work like Uncle Wang ?
You little rascal !
Ouch, it hurts.
Uncle Wang,
I won't bring you wine today.
You are getting old, you can't drink every day.
6 years later
Be careful.
Immortal,
thank you for coming.
Kid,
come here.
Excellent bones,
his body is made to cultivate.
You you let me take him in as my disciple ?
Of course.
Gladly !
Of course !
Xiao Niu,
it doesn't matter if you don't become an Immortal.
You can always come back home !
It's snowing !
It's getting too cold.
How could it be snowing at this time of the year ?
When it snows, New Year is near !
Go back home,
stop playing outside.
But it's great !
And they're gone...
This isn't normal snow.
It has killing intent ?
Yay it's thundering !
When I grow up I want to be an Immortal too.
Immortals are so powerful !
A thunder spell ?
There's a huge restriction here ?
What the hell ?!
The reincarnation cycle stems from the daoist belief that birth is not the beginning and that death is not the end. When a person dies, their soul leaves their body and enters the Yellow Spings, also known as the underworld, and takes the Reincarnation River to be reborn.\NLife and death in a world governed by the reincarnation cycle are just steps of the soul's journey. Moving on to the next life is just a natural part of the law of the heavens.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.